## Franco Rezabek

### Infrastructure Engineer at Amazon Development Centre

rezabek2011@gmail.com

## Summary

Experienced Infrastructure Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python, Linux System Administration, SaltStack, Docker, and Amazon Web Services (AWS). Strong information technology professional with a BSc (Hons) focused in Computer Science with Foundation from University of Westminster.

# Experience

## Infrastructure Engineer at Amazon Development Centre, London

April 2017 - Present

### IT Support Engineer at Amazon

March 2015 - March 2017 (2 years 1 month)

#### System Administrator at HighOps

July 2014 - February 2015 (8 months)

#### Senior Data Engineer at intaRack Solutions Limited

September 2013 - July 2014 (11 months)

#### **Data Engineer**

October 2011 - September 2013 (2 years)

#### IT Support at Standard Bank Group

May 2008 - October 2011 (3 years 6 months)

### Education

## **University of Westminster**

BSc (Hons), Computer Science with Foundation, 2009 - 2013